"Honjo"
One, please!
That's 500 yen!
Two for me, please!
Sure! 1,000 yen!
Looks like it's not even a contest.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Girls, get ready!
--Yeah!
Wha--?!
We made these outfits while
you guys worked on the manga!
We'll do whatever it takes to win!
"Shido A Live"
Circle "Ratatoskr" here!
Please line up to buy your copy!
That circle's got a bunch of cute girls.
They're not in the catalog.
Hmm? What have we got here?
Ooh! Thank you!
--Huh? No, I...
--That's 500 yen, please!
Uh, right... I'll take it.
Whoa! Thank you!
S-Sure.
I guess that works, too.
"Line Starts Here"
The line starts here!
Request! Please form two lines!
It got busy all of a sudden.
Two, please.
S-Sure! Wait, huh?!
Yup. It's the Ratatoskr crew.
So we're using shills now?
Hey, Tohka! We made it!
This place is packed!
That's so lame.
Mm! Thanks for coming, guys!
You know it! Since you asked,
I had to come!
Mm-hmm! Comico sounded fun, too.
Hmm? Even Itsuka's here!
You helping Tohka?
Y-Yeah.
Hmm? I feel like the protagonist
looks awfully like Itsuka.
That's so lame.
U-Um, but it's fiction! Any similarity
to real people or events is coincidental!
Thanks, Captain Obvious.
Spirits? A secret organization?
That's so lame.
Origami? It's rare for you to ask a favor.
Captain, Mikie, Mildred...
Thanks for coming.
Hey, I feel like I've
seen those girls before...
You haven't.
You seem different lately, Origami.
I'm not.
Those people...
They don't remember the world
before I changed history?
No, but we Spirits remember 'cuz we're
connected to you through Spirit power.
Five boxes left... And her?
It's no use! We'll never win!
Of course not. These people want
one thing--a good read.
You stood no chance against me in such
short a time, even with your tricks.
It's not over yet!
We're just getting started!
Hmm?
"Miku here~ I'm at Comico doing
a handshake event at Ratatoskr
(West A-20/5). Take a photo with me~~~! #comico"
It's showtime!
"Submit"
It's actually her!
No way! Why is she here?!
Can we really shake your hand?!
Thanks for all your support,
everyone! I-It's true!
Miku, are you sure?
But you hate men!
Darling and everyone else gave their best,
so I refuse to stand by!
I'm stepping up like Natsumi!
I wanna do my part, too!
Thank you!
Hmm? Not bad. That girl's famous, huh?
Yeah. She's our treasured idol.
But can you catch up?
Yeah, we'll win. Not only for
our sake, but for yours, too.
Listen to you!
Maybe. Only if you win, though.
Honjo?
Um...
T-Takajo...
It's been a while.
I had to come when I heard
you were participating.
U-Uh...
Kotori, did you know she'd come?
No.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but there's something I have to ask.
Have I done something to upset you
without knowing it?
If so, I'd like to apologize.
Th-That's not...
Though, even if you hate me,
I'll always look forward
to reading your works.
Mm...
I finally get it.
You like her, don't you?
Huh?! Wh-What are you saying, Boy?
You didn't distance yourself
'cuz you found out her dark side.
You're just afraid you'll get curious
and look someday...
That you'll learn about her dark side.
You pulled away,
afraid to be let down, right?
Hah! You don't know what
you're talking about, Boy!
Five hundred yen, please!
Then explain yourself!
For hating people,
you sure get along with 'em!
Would you shut up?
Focus on your booth!
Two, right?
--Sorry, but no can do!
--Hey, Shido! Help out!
I wanna win 'cuz I wanna help you!
Ignoring the problem ain't gonna help!
Here's your change!
So what if I'm afraid?!
As if someone who can peep into
people's lives could make friends!
You won't know till you try!
Would you open your heart
to someone who can peep into
all your dark secrets and private life?!
I can see you on the toilet or
in the bath around the clock!
No one will be my friend knowing that!
Wh-What's so funny?!
Sorry, but that doesn't even faze me.
"Line Starts Here"
Privacy? What's that?
In fact, you're a saint for even caring.
Huh?
If you wanna peep on me, go ahead!
I'm never gonna hate you for it!
We're down to one copy!
Shido, it's our last one!
--Thank you!
Ratatoskr: sold out!
Honjo: sold out!
Now then, it seems we had a tie.
Ah, fine. Since you guys
put up a fight, I'll read it.
Ugh, good grief.
Hmm? I see...
"Shido A Live"
A tale about Shido Itsuka
saving Spirits...
It's better than I thought
it would be, but still...
It just packs too much in.
With eight Spirits, there're not enough
pages to like the main character.
Well, it's not bad
considering the time crunch.
How did they even make it in time?
I wanna show that dummy Nia, too:
That friends are a wonderful thing.
The whole story was true?
Even the things he said...
Nia...
What did you think of our manga?
Hmm. It's all right,
but it's a bit naïve to think
I'd fall for you with just that.
Still, since it moved me a little,
I'm fine with giving you another shot.
--Huh?
--For crying out loud!
I'll go on another date!
If you're a man, make it count!
--Shido!
--Awesome!
You did it, Darling!
It's still too early to celebrate.
But, Boy--
N-Nia?
The spatial quake alarm!
Nia! What's wrong?!
Reine, what's happening?!
Spirit Level: Category E! Nia's inverting!
Spatial quake warning. Please evacuate
to the nearest shelter immediately.
Just as planned: Sister inverted.
But why, Ike?
For five years,
we put Sister through
unthinkable physical and mental agony.
And yet, not once
could we make her invert.
Before us, Sister had already
lost her faith in humanity.
That's why I allowed her to escape.
So, the micro Realizer
you planted in her brain...
Was to make her forget
everything we did to her.
But the instant she opened up to Shido
and regained her trust in humanity,
she remembered
five terrible years of suffering.
It's just like glass--the higher the fall,
the easier it breaks.
I'm counting on you, too.
Lend Ellen a hand.
Beelzebub.
--That's--!
--Careful, Shido!
It's from her Demon King.
Metatron!
Whatever this is, we can't let it be.
Let us take care of these
while you get to Nia and--!
Sorry, but I can't allow it.
Ellen!
Given your timing, I take it
you guys are responsible for this.
Your Demon King's power is troublesome.
Let's finish this quickly.
Sandalphon!
Kaguya, Yuzuru, and Miku take Ellen!
Origami, Yoshino, and Natsumi help Shido!
--Right!
Nia!
Wh-What's this? I can't move!
Future Entry!
Leave it to me! Zadkiel!
You guys are in our way!
Haniel!
H-Huh?!
Wh-What?!
Future Entry again?!
Shido!
Zadkiel!
Shido used Zadkiel!
I can move?! Oh, I get it!
'Cuz that wasn't written down?
Now I can fight! Sandalphon!
Nia!
Wait... If I use Miku's Gabriel...!
Shi... do...
Hang on! I'm gonna save you!
I won't allow it.
Nia!
Why are you here, Artemisia Ashcroft?
Artemisia?!
Isaac Westcott?!
Long time no see, Shido Itsuka.
I'm glad you're doing well.
Ah, it's marvelous!
A crystal of inverted Spirit power--
Qlipha!
At last, I take one great stride
towards my deepest desires!
No way! He absorbed a Sephirah?!
That's right, Shido Itsuka.
Just like you gained
the powers of eight Spirits.
Beelzebub.
Oh, how curious.
Just by touching a Demon King,
you know exactly how to use its power.
Ike!
Ellen, behold one of the majestic
Demon Kings which shall light our path!
But one is simply not enough
to satisfy our ambitions.
Shido! You okay?!
Yeah! But Nia was...!
Ellen, we achieved our goal.
Let's call it a day.
Are you sure?
Even my body will struggle to absorb
multiple Demon Kings at once.
Besides, it would be such a waste
not to savor them one by one.
We will meet again soon,
Shido Itsuka... and Spirits.
Someday, I'll make you invert
and take your Qlipha.
Try to enjoy your final days of peace.
Nia!
Nia! Nia! Hang in there!
Wait, Shido! It's faint,
but I sense her Spirit power!
What?!
Just before she was stabbed,
you pulled part of her consciousness back.
At that point,
she wasn't fully inverted anymore.
She probably has a fragment
of Sephirah left in her body.
In other words, you can seal her.
Please, Nia! Open your heart to me!
I don't care if you use
all my power, so...
Open your eyes, Nia!
--Nia!
Nia!
You don't have to shout. I can hear you.
Thank... you...
First sunrise of the year!
Boy... Thank you for everything.
Don't mention it.
Everyone's been helping me, too.
I had time to think while I recovered...
...and I wanna talk to Takajo again.
Yeah, you should.
She's a good person, probably.
"Probably"?
It's weird. It stinks that my power was
taken, but I'm kinda at peace with it.
I had Raziel for, like, 30 years,
but maybe the power's too much for me.
Thirty years? You became
a Spirit that long ago?
It's 27 or 28 to be precise.
Don't I look good for my age?
Your Spirit power probably
halted your aging.
But now, you'll age normally,
so watch out!
Oh, by the way...
When did you guys become Spirits?
Five years ago for me.
I did about one year ago.
I did recently.
The rest of us are Pure Spirits.
"Pure Spirits"?
But Spirits were all humans
in the beginning, right?
"Episode 03:
'What's Yours Is Mine.'"
See the sky! See the stars! See Mukuro!
It's a new Spirit, floating in the cosmos!
Next time: "Space Spirit."
When Earth is in trouble,
Shido will rise! Shido will fight!
"Episode 04: 'Space Spirit.'"